{"CatCo": {"type": "ORG", "context": "T FOR PROPOSAL\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nCONTENT DEVELOPMENT PARTNER\nCatCo\n\n\n\n\n\nProposals Due By: 05/05/24\nTABLE OF CONTENTS...", "token": "[[REDACTED_1089ec4b]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "CatCo BACKGROUND": {"type": "ORG", "context": " 05/05/24\nTABLE OF CONTENTS\n       \nINTRODUCTION\n\nCatCo BACKGROUND\n\nThe CatCo makes up the largest railcar repair ne...", "token": "[[REDACTED_c99e425c]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Mechanical Repairs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "f tank and freight car repair services including:\nMechanical Repairs\nValves and fittings service\nCompliance testing\nCo...", "token": "[[REDACTED_c8b5cb2a]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "PURPOSE": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ility in rail equipment maintenance and repair.\n \nPURPOSE AND GOALS\n\nCatCo is seeking to supplement the cap...", "token": "[[REDACTED_8cb13005]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Learning and Development Team": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lement the capacity and expertise of our internal Learning and Development Team by working with an external content development p...", "token": "[[REDACTED_14efe0d9]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Technology Integration and Innovative Solutions": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d company to create effective learning programs.\n\nTechnology Integration and Innovative Solutions \nIncorporate multimedia assets and innovative app...", "token": "[[REDACTED_fd8efd84]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Safety, Health": {"type": "ORG", "context": "view of the procedure or specification document.\n\nSafety, Health, and Environment (SHE)\nThis training is focused o...", "token": "[[REDACTED_bb9c6982]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Personal Protective Equipment": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ad car repair shop. Topics could include specific Personal Protective Equipment specifications such as Clear Face Shield, Hazardo...", "token": "[[REDACTED_a0c68dc4]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Hazardous Chemical Awareness": {"type": "ORG", "context": "uipment specifications such as Clear Face Shield, Hazardous Chemical Awareness such as Nitrogen Awareness, Job Related Safety su...", "token": "[[REDACTED_6a7558af]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Nitrogen Awareness": {"type": "ORG", "context": "Face Shield, Hazardous Chemical Awareness such as Nitrogen Awareness, Job Related Safety such as Welding, among others...", "token": "[[REDACTED_42bdb11e]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "eLearning": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ing topics are delivered through a combination of eLearning, Classroom Training, and On-the-Job Training.\n\nTA...", "token": "[[REDACTED_62219325]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Repair Shops": {"type": "ORG", "context": "intenance work on railroad cars in our network of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the...", "token": "[[REDACTED_01f08c46]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Project Management": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ional design process and instructional designers.\nProject Management for assigned instructional design projects.\nDesig...", "token": "[[REDACTED_154ea420]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Software": {"type": "ORG", "context": "t matter experts to distill critical information.\nSoftware, licensing, and certifications necessary for deve...", "token": "[[REDACTED_7e934afe]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Media Integration": {"type": "ORG", "context": " feedback into the final product.\n\nTechnology and Media Integration\nSCORM compliant content that can be delivered and...", "token": "[[REDACTED_de84093b]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "SCORM": {"type": "ORG", "context": " final product.\n\nTechnology and Media Integration\nSCORM compliant content that can be delivered and track...", "token": "[[REDACTED_5196a0a7]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the Rockstar Learning Management System": {"type": "ORG", "context": "content that can be delivered and tracked through the Rockstar Learning Management System.\nContent compatibility across multiple common bro...", "token": "[[REDACTED_1067e98d]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Project Management and Communication": {"type": "ORG", "context": "e common browsers (Chrome, Edge, Firefox, etc.).\n\nProject Management and Communication\nDedicated Project Manager and project management ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_8d70a2d1]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Review Processes": {"type": "ORG", "context": "e delivery.\n\nSubject Matter Expert Engagement and Review Processes\nClearly defined and streamlined methodology for p...", "token": "[[REDACTED_13f2f05f]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Instructional Design and Subject Matter Expert": {"type": "ORG", "context": "in nature to CatCo with similar training needs. \n\nInstructional Design and Subject Matter Expert engagement models and processes to include:\nA doc...", "token": "[[REDACTED_e648c533]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "SME": {"type": "ORG", "context": " clearly defined, and streamlined methodology for SME partnership that demonstrates efficiency and effe...", "token": "[[REDACTED_3baa9b5a]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Communication": {"type": "ORG", "context": "as well as any other support structures in place.\nCommunication and escalation cadence and pathways.\n\nReferences ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_fff33add]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "MN 22222": {"type": "ORG", "context": "N\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \nCONFIDENTI...", "token": "[[REDACTED_f783de03]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Non-Disclosure Agreement": {"type": "ORG", "context": "submission, the respondent agrees to enter into a Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) with CatCo. The purpose of the NDA is to pr...", "token": "[[REDACTED_9f76a0b2]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "NDA": {"type": "ORG", "context": " agrees to enter into a Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) with CatCo. The purpose of the NDA is to protect...", "token": "[[REDACTED_65852a3c]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the Non-Disclosure Agreement": {"type": "ORG", "context": "fication process, confidentiality, as outlined in the Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA), will be maintained.\n\nThis notification pro...", "token": "[[REDACTED_9aa7055c]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "3 years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "ailcar repair network in North America.  For over 3 years, we have repaired the tank and freight railcars r...", "token": "[[REDACTED_121d106e]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "each day": {"type": "DATE", "context": "ilcars responsible for transporting tons of goods each day, serving every major sector of the economy. We ar...", "token": "[[REDACTED_6765f18e]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "one hundred years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "linings\nCleaning\nTank car modification\n\nWith over one hundred years of experience, we are proud to be a trusted name ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_daed6881]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Valves": {"type": "GPE", "context": "car repair services including:\nMechanical Repairs\nValves and fittings service\nCompliance testing\nCoatings ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_f6671b29]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the United States": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ilroad cars in our network of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the training is focused on b...", "token": "[[REDACTED_aa0fa115]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Mexico": {"type": "GPE", "context": "work of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the training is focused on building new...", "token": "[[REDACTED_e0748041]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Manderville": {"type": "GPE", "context": "CT INFORMATION\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \n...", "token": "[[REDACTED_2295bec4]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "GOALS": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "l equipment maintenance and repair.\n \nPURPOSE AND GOALS\n\nCatCo is seeking to supplement the capacity and ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_07f6e7c3]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Subject Matter Expert Engagement": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "bility to manage timelines for on-time delivery.\n\nSubject Matter Expert Engagement and Review Processes\nClearly defined and streamli...", "token": "[[REDACTED_7e78c088]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Proposal": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ent to meet requirements across countries.\n\nPrice Proposal and Fee Structure\nReliable fee structure with fin...", "token": "[[REDACTED_8d95823f]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Emphasis": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "provided for, and breakdown of client industries.\nEmphasis on any customers similar in nature to CatCo with ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_b93feb83]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Joe Manderson": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ity to flex-up when needed.\n\nCONTACT INFORMATION\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmander...", "token": "[[REDACTED_1caf3e0d]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "jmanderson@catco.com": {"type": "EMAIL", "context": "nderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \nCONFIDENTIALITY STATEMENT\n\nCatC...", "token": "[[REDACTED_572ea315]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "jamderson@catco.com": {"type": "EMAIL", "context": "quested information via email to Joe Manderson to jamderson@catco.com by the submission date on the cover page of this ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_c757b70f]]", "action": "IGNORE"}}