{"COMPANY": {"type": "ORG", "context": "tribution Management.\nAbout International Markets\nCOMPANY is a business division within CatCo comprised of ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_774f3949]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Catco": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ltant, has been working with various parts of the Catco organisation for the past 9 years, and has played...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_cca2f18d]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "International Markets": {"type": "ORG", "context": "within the area of Distribution Management.\nAbout International Markets\nCOMPANY is a business division within CatCo compr...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_63d5b2fc]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "CatCo": {"type": "ORG", "context": "nagers, responsible for Distribution Management.  CatCo years ago, following a strategic review of our vi...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_453728d7]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Commercial": {"type": "ORG", "context": " global markets. \nWe are coming together with our Commercial colleagues in CatCo markets, to drive excellence ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_2937bbcf]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Pause 4 Paws’": {"type": "ORG", "context": "esponsibilities are universal and are detailed in Pause 4 Paws’ pawbook. \nThere are approximately 22 commercial r...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_26a2e7dc]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Regional General Managers": {"type": "ORG", "context": "all heads of markets (Market General Managers and Regional General Managers) as being part of our professional commercial com...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_b171bbe5]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Brief": {"type": "ORG", "context": "art of our professional commercial community.\nThe Brief\nWe strive to enhance the capabilities of our Comm...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_97e6dbb0]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the Distributor Partners": {"type": "ORG", "context": "omprehensive overview of our ways of working with the Distributor Partners took place.  Tools and processes were created and...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_863471f0]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the DEX Academy": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ntify the learning partner we work with to create the DEX Academy. \nThe vision is a self-sustained learning experie...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_49b6eb94]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Academy": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ou to support the development and delivery of the Academy.\nThe blended approach should allow for both self-...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_5405c787]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "The Global DEX Academy": {"type": "ORG", "context": "owth, and excellence in Distribution Management. \nThe Global DEX Academy is envisioned to be a structured, progressive lea...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c4013e00]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Land Lady": {"type": "ORG", "context": "pporting the DEX programme over the last 2 years. Land Lady will be available to work with you to support the...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_1cf136ac]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "DEX": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d has played a significant role in supporting the DEX programme over the last 2 years. Land Lady will b...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_14aa8f4a]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "SME": {"type": "ORG", "context": "nd develop problem-solving skills. We can provide SME’s to inform this creation.\nPeer Coaching and Ment...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_995ee87d]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Distribution Management": {"type": "ORG", "context": " exceptional performance and improvement in their Distribution Management capabilities. This can be done through certificat...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c14c16b6]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the Distribution Excellence Academy": {"type": "ORG", "context": "or support you can offer to ensure the success of the Distribution Excellence Academy.\n\nTimeline\n\n...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_9abb8666]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the United States": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ithin Catco with approximately 44 people based in the United States and Europe.  Our teams in these key countries are...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_0c224858]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "France": {"type": "GPE", "context": "owth across European developing markets including France and Portugal  This region has 12% of the World’s ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_87a51f8b]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "Portugal": {"type": "GPE", "context": " European developing markets including France and Portugal  This region has 12% of the World’s population, t...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_f095f998]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "London": {"type": "GPE", "context": "llection of small overseas markets based from the London, England.  All commercial roles are ‘in-market’ f...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_d7c7bc38]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "England": {"type": "GPE", "context": " of small overseas markets based from the London, England.  All commercial roles are ‘in-market’ focused wi...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_1a746a42]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "12%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "ts including France and Portugal  This region has 12% of the World’s population, though overall GDP con...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_898566e8]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "years ago": {"type": "DATE", "context": ", responsible for Distribution Management.  CatCo years ago, following a strategic review of our vision, we r...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_df0f1034]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the past 9 years": {"type": "DATE", "context": " with various parts of the Catco organisation for the past 9 years, and has played a significant role in supporting ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_cf0ccec0]]", "action": "IGNORE"}, "the last 2 years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "ificant role in supporting the DEX programme over the last 2 years. Land Lady will be available to work with you to ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_fca2561d]]", "action": "IGNORE"}}