{"Bark Barn": {"type": "ORG", "context": "the Schedule, entitled “FAR Clauses”, and in turn Bark Barn is required to insert these clauses in all subcon...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_ba1b3408]]"}, "Department of Commerce": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ent.\nPrime Contract means Company’s contract with Department of Commerce\n\n\n[REDACTED]\n\nII.   FAR Flowdown Clauses for Subc...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_28e18858]]"}, "the Department of Commerce": {"type": "ORG", "context": "endor that attaches the corresponding notice from the Department of Commerce terminating the Prime Contract (for purposes of P...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_09bdbfe2]]"}, "Louisville": {"type": "GPE", "context": "federal government. Bark Barn is headquartered in Louisville, KY.\n\nA. Background\nAs a Department of Commerce c...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_0bc6c28a]]"}, "KY": {"type": "GPE", "context": "rnment. Bark Barn is headquartered in Louisville, KY.\n\nA. Background\nAs a Department of Commerce contr...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_84ad3cd7]]"}, ".": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ment. Bark Barn is headquartered in Louisville, KY.\n\nA. Background\nAs a Department of Commerce contra...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_8ee6c80c]]"}, "Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ne Year Option Years, with the options awarded by Help More Dogs based on performance.\nA Straight 5 year Base Term...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_5e63be15]]"}, "The Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "onal Resources \n\nA. Instructional Design Creator \nThe Help More Dogs currently uses a separate platform to design cour...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_bbbdfef0]]"}, "the Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ty to provide a presentation, Vendor will provide the Help More Dogs a detailed agenda prior to the presentation.\n\n\nC....", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_4088bf36]]"}, "Help More Dogs’s": {"type": "ORG", "context": " with other parties for any other purpose without Help More Dogs’s written permission as required in the non-disclos...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_63747a85]]"}, "no later than 6/30/23": {"type": "DATE", "context": "dential.\n\nB. Timeline\nPlease deliver the proposal no later than 6/30/23.\nIf a response to this RFP is not received by the...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_7cea984c]]"}, "Guy McMann": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ions regarding this RFP must be sent via email to Guy McMann at the above email addresses no later than 5:00pm...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_82f9cfc5]]"}, "Vendor": {"type": "ORG", "context": "rection, return such Personal Data.  Upon request Vendor shall provide a written certification that the re...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_51cfbd57]]"}, "30%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "r rating will be based on the following criteria:\n30% Technical - Ability to meet the minimum technolog...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_cc566436]]"}, ".\n35%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "h, and cost at the end of the appropriate sections.\n35% Cost - Solution that provides best value\n20% Non-...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_f2bbc7e5]]"}, "20%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "ons.\n35% Cost - Solution that provides best value\n20% Non-Operational Business Requirements\nTechnology ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_340c606d]]"}, "15%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "a, Past Performance and References will count for 15% of the vendor’s scoring. The following questions ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_1c32d32e]]"}, "the last four years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "hat have been provided comparable services within the last four years.\n\nThe award of the contract to the winning vendor...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c6ab279b]]"}, "Microsoft": {"type": "ORG", "context": "rts must be generated for all training content in Microsoft Excel format. The following information must be r...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_eed797b6]]"}, "Adobe": {"type": "ORG", "context": "osal response should be provided in both Word and Adobe PDF.\n\n...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_da8a7fd7]]"}, "monthly": {"type": "DATE", "context": "t Assignments: Knowledge Assessments are assigned monthly utilizing randomized questions created from all i...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_b3a94b3d]]"}, "two weeks": {"type": "DATE", "context": "lete” courses, an additional notification is sent two weeks prior to due date and again when it is past due. ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c31bfbf2]]"}, "the Help More Dogs Learning and Leadership Development Department": {"type": "ORG", "context": "esponses\n\nThe following services are required for the Help More Dogs Learning and Leadership Development Department. Vendors are to provide their best solution for s...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_93b5cdd5]]"}, "Bark Barn-Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "DS requirement will require a Q&A session between Bark Barn-Help More Dogs and prospective vendor technology/security teams ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_caea76c6]]"}, "the Help More Dogs and Vendor": {"type": "ORG", "context": " Bark Barn, acting in its capacity as operator of the Help More Dogs and Vendor and will contain this language: “This Agreement i...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_ad706498]]"}, "the  Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "age: “This Agreement is solely for the benefit of the  Help More Dogs (“Help More Dogs”).  The  Help More Dogs operates...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_ec36e0eb]]"}, "The  Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "nefit of the  Help More Dogs (“Help More Dogs”).  The  Help More Dogs operates under the Department of Commerce contrac...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_dd0e5591]]"}, "Bark Barning": {"type": "ORG", "context": " contract number REDACTED to manage operations of Bark Barning on REDACTED bases overseas.”  \n\nIf your company i...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_1be21449]]"}, "CLINET": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ion of a Bark Barn proprietary contract utilizing CLINET standard terms and conditions following Bark Barn...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c901ab34]]"}, "LLC": {"type": "ORG", "context": "f vendor’s contracting entity (as in corporation, LLC, GmBH), the date the entity was established, and ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_68af4080]]"}, "GmBH": {"type": "ORG", "context": "dor’s contracting entity (as in corporation, LLC, GmBH), the date the entity was established, and locati...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_a5a8e1cf]]"}, "Services": {"type": "ORG", "context": " regulations and legal requirements relate to the Services (all such laws, rules, regulatory guidance, regul...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_7754720a]]"}, "REDACTED": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lizing facilities or personnel located outside of REDACTED, disclose which facilities and all locations in t...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_8880b71a]]"}, "Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ntract means this Agreement.\nPrime Contract means Company’s contract with Department of Commerce\n\n\n[REDACTE...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_6bb150da]]"}, "annual": {"type": "DATE", "context": "actors successfully complete and implement, on an annual basis, such mandatory training as Company may req...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_ccadd65f]]"}, "the Department of Commerce’s": {"type": "ORG", "context": "-Help More Dogs has certain obligations to manage the Department of Commerce’s  Help More Dogs under the  Help More Dogs Prime C...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_0bbb0eff]]"}, "DATE": {"type": "DATE", "context": "Barn Prime base contract begins DATE, and expires DATE, with (i) eight (8) performance option years expi...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_29882f74]]"}, "60 days": {"type": "DATE", "context": " with Bark Barn, such termination to be effective 60 days following delivery of such notice. Bark Barn sole...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_1c0a24e1]]"}, "the final day": {"type": "DATE", "context": "liverables provided and services rendered through the final day on which the Vendor provided deliverables and per...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_133fea95]]"}, "WEBSITE": {"type": "ORG", "context": "any Renewal Terms. The REGULATION may be found at WEBSITE. Vendor further understands it is responsible for...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_39c9eab9]]"}, "Subcontractors": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ULATION requirements by Vendor and all identified Subcontractors. Failure to discharge this obligation may be cons...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_662c6674]]"}, "the lesser of five (5) working days": {"type": "DATE", "context": "ovide any information requested by Company within the lesser of five (5) working days of such request or in accordance with timescales ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_9acd3834]]"}, "the   REDACTED Economic Area": {"type": "GPE", "context": "r shall not transfer any Personal Data outside of the   REDACTED Economic Area or any other relevant jurisdiction in providing S...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_55b8f1ad]]"}, "Human Resource (": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ifications:\n\nOrganization support for Accounting, Human Resource (HR) and/or Payroll in Italy for entities headquart...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_12704cdd]]"}, "Payroll": {"type": "ORG", "context": "upport for Accounting, Human Resource (HR) and/or Payroll in Italy for entities headquartered outside of It...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_a6b5f29b]]"}, "Italy": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ll in Italy for entities headquartered outside of Italy.\n\nPreferably a Financial Services organization.\n\n...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c7ba046a]]"}, "Three (3) year": {"type": "DATE", "context": " a bid for one or both contract term scenarios. \n\nThree (3) year Base Term plus two (2) One Year Option Years, wit...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_dfa03829]]"}, "5 year": {"type": "DATE", "context": "y Help More Dogs based on performance.\nA Straight 5 year Base Term.\n\nVendors must include any volume or te...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_9c8cb5e2]]"}}