{"CatCo": {"type": "ORG", "context": "T FOR PROPOSAL\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nCONTENT DEVELOPMENT PARTNER\nCatCo\n\n\n\n\n\nProposals Due By: 05/05/24\nTABLE OF CONTENTS...", "token": "[[REDACTED_41ecff3c]]"}, "05/05/24": {"type": "DATE", "context": " DEVELOPMENT PARTNER\nCatCo\n\n\n\n\n\nProposals Due By: 05/05/24\nTABLE OF CONTENTS\n       \nINTRODUCTION\n\nCatCo BAC...", "token": "[[REDACTED_f14bb31e]]"}, "over 3 years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "est railcar repair network in North America.  For over 3 years, we have repaired the tank and freight railcars r...", "token": "[[REDACTED_f086bab8]]"}, "each day": {"type": "DATE", "context": "ilcars responsible for transporting tons of goods each day, serving every major sector of the economy. We ar...", "token": "[[REDACTED_b3920762]]"}, "PURPOSE AND GOALS": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ility in rail equipment maintenance and repair.\n \nPURPOSE AND GOALS\n\nCatCo is seeking to supplement the capacity and ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_1c072f64]]"}, "Learning and Development Team": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lement the capacity and expertise of our internal Learning and Development Team by working with an external content development p...", "token": "[[REDACTED_78dffa3c]]"}, "Technology Integration": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d company to create effective learning programs.\n\nTechnology Integration and Innovative Solutions \nIncorporate multimedia ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_24b3b32c]]"}, "Repair Shops": {"type": "ORG", "context": "intenance work on railroad cars in our network of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the...", "token": "[[REDACTED_da50ae7d]]"}, "the United States": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ilroad cars in our network of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the training is focused on b...", "token": "[[REDACTED_3e34ace6]]"}, "Mexico": {"type": "GPE", "context": "work of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the training is focused on building new...", "token": "[[REDACTED_11bddf6d]]"}, "SCOPE OF SERVICES": {"type": "ORG", "context": "at is easily digestible and readily actionable.\n\n\nSCOPE OF SERVICES\n\nCatCo is seeking a content development partner t...", "token": "[[REDACTED_abdeaaaf]]"}, "Rockstar": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ent that can be delivered and tracked through the Rockstar Learning Management System.\nContent compatibility...", "token": "[[REDACTED_08251432]]"}, "Joe Manderson": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ity to flex-up when needed.\n\nCONTACT INFORMATION\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmander...", "token": "[[REDACTED_3c9a7e83]]"}, "Manderville": {"type": "GPE", "context": "CT INFORMATION\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \n...", "token": "[[REDACTED_99a538c7]]"}, "MN": {"type": "GPE", "context": "N\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \nCONF...", "token": "[[REDACTED_961d0f13]]"}, "jmanderson@catco.com": {"type": "EMAIL", "context": "nderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \nCONFIDENTIALITY STATEMENT\n\nCatC...", "token": "[[REDACTED_32521131]]"}, "jamderson@catco.com": {"type": "EMAIL", "context": "quested information via email to Joe Manderson to jamderson@catco.com by the submission date on the cover page of this ...", "token": "[[REDACTED_725ac97a]]"}}