{"CatCo": {"type": "ORG", "context": " evaluation team, comprising representatives from CatCo, will thoroughly review and assess each proposal ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_7bdb517a]]"}, "05/05/24": {"type": "DATE", "context": " DEVELOPMENT PARTNER\nCatCo\n\n\n\n\n\nProposals Due By: 05/05/24\nTABLE OF CONTENTS\n       \nINTRODUCTION\n\nCatCo BAC...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_d9084ad1]]"}, "over 3 years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "est railcar repair network in North America.  For over 3 years, we have repaired the tank and freight railcars r...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_edcf6666]]"}, "each day": {"type": "DATE", "context": "ilcars responsible for transporting tons of goods each day, serving every major sector of the economy. We ar...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_9c7f938d]]"}, "PURPOSE AND GOALS": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ility in rail equipment maintenance and repair.\n \nPURPOSE AND GOALS\n\nCatCo is seeking to supplement the capacity and ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_d1746f9e]]"}, "Learning and Development Team": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lement the capacity and expertise of our internal Learning and Development Team by working with an external content development p...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_26b2fb6f]]"}, "Technology Integration": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d company to create effective learning programs.\n\nTechnology Integration and Innovative Solutions \nIncorporate multimedia ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_9f75d32c]]"}, "Repair Shops": {"type": "ORG", "context": "intenance work on railroad cars in our network of Repair Shops across the United States and Mexico.\n\nMuch of the...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_3c7abaa8]]"}, "the United States": {"type": "GPE", "context": " create content internationally (minimally across the United States and Mexico).\nAbility to adapt content culturally ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_9a8a1956]]"}, "Mexico": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ationally (minimally across the United States and Mexico).\nAbility to adapt content culturally through use...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_c32242be]]"}, "SCOPE OF SERVICES": {"type": "ORG", "context": "at is easily digestible and readily actionable.\n\n\nSCOPE OF SERVICES\n\nCatCo is seeking a content development partner t...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_31eae5a7]]"}, "Rockstar": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ent that can be delivered and tracked through the Rockstar Learning Management System.\nContent compatibility...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_912fb396]]"}, "Joe Manderson": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "S\n\nPlease send requested information via email to Joe Manderson to jamderson@catco.com by the submission date on ...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_5e331ebd]]"}, "Manderville": {"type": "GPE", "context": "CT INFORMATION\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \n...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_e48a2bfd]]"}, "MN": {"type": "GPE", "context": "N\n\nJoe Manderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \nCONF...", "confidence": 0.9, "token": "[[REDACTED_989a5e0c]]"}, "jmanderson@catco.com": {"type": "EMAIL", "context": "nderson\n999 S. State Street\nManderville, MN 22222\njmanderson@catco.com\n(555) 555 - 5555 \nCONFIDENTIALITY STATEMENT\n\nCatC...", "confidence": 1.0, "token": "[[REDACTED_c45e3052]]"}, "jamderson@catco.com": {"type": "EMAIL", "context": "quested information via email to Joe Manderson to jamderson@catco.com by the submission date on the cover page of this ...", "confidence": 1.0, "token": "[[REDACTED_5540fd93]]"}}