{"Learning Management System": {"type": "ORG", "context": "etitive price. The target environment is a single Learning Management System (LMS) providing seamless delivery of Web-Based Tr", "token": "[[REDACTED_b6a2f917]]"}, "LMS": {"type": "ORG", "context": " learning content and capabilities offered by the LMS. Minimum of five administrative licenses. \n\nThe c", "token": "[[REDACTED_b328c6a7]]"}, "a Department of Commerce (Department of Commerce": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ts  \n\n\n\n\n\nOverview\n\nThe Help more Dogs program is a Department of Commerce (Department of Commerce) program operated by Bark Barn. The Program opera", "token": "[[REDACTED_c0b220ea]]"}, "Bark Barn": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ective 60 days following delivery of such notice. Bark Barn sole and exclusive liability to the Vendor for te", "token": "[[REDACTED_c86d61ae]]"}, "Program": {"type": "ORG", "context": "t of Commerce) program operated by Bark Barn. The Program operates a bank which offers banking services and", "token": "[[REDACTED_31e26b7e]]"}, "ATM": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ffers banking services and a robust dual currency ATM network to authorized Department of Commerce and ", "token": "[[REDACTED_0f0cf588]]"}, "Department of Commerce": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ent.\nPrime Contract means Company’s contract with Department of Commerce\n\n\n[REDACTED]\n\nII.   FAR Flowdown Clauses for Subc", "token": "[[REDACTED_ee9a8dea]]"}, "Department of Commerce Bark Barn": {"type": "ORG", "context": "anizations, and commands in overseas locations. \n\nDepartment of Commerce Bark Barn has 60 branches and two offices. The bank associa", "token": "[[REDACTED_dcc01cdd]]"}, "the Department of Commerce": {"type": "ORG", "context": "endor that attaches the corresponding notice from the Department of Commerce terminating the Prime Contract (for purposes of P", "token": "[[REDACTED_9a5fb708]]"}, "Louisville": {"type": "GPE", "context": "federal government. Bark Barn is headquartered in Louisville, KY.\n\nA. Background\nAs a Department of Commerce c", "token": "[[REDACTED_84d327f8]]"}, "KY": {"type": "GPE", "context": "rnment. Bark Barn is headquartered in Louisville, KY.\n\nA. Background\nAs a Department of Commerce contr", "token": "[[REDACTED_1bd39323]]"}, "Web-Based Training Modules": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ement System (LMS) providing seamless delivery of Web-Based Training Modules, learning documents retrieval, and automated crea", "token": "[[REDACTED_90fd0cbc]]"}, "the Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": " Bark Barn, acting in its capacity as operator of the Help More Dogs and Vendor and will contain this language: “This ", "token": "[[REDACTED_8f91857f]]"}, "the Confidentiality and Information Protection": {"type": "ORG", "context": "t you remain legally obligated under the terms of the Confidentiality and Information Protection sections of your existing contract.\n\nRequirement:", "token": "[[REDACTED_7e0e413d]]"}, "B. Timeline\nPlease": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "s to keep all information strictly confidential.\n\nB. Timeline\nPlease deliver the proposal no later than 6/30/23.\nIf a ", "token": "[[REDACTED_ed7f2b90]]"}, "Guy McMann": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ions regarding this RFP must be sent via email to Guy McMann at the above email addresses no later than 5:00pm", "token": "[[REDACTED_51800809]]"}, "Vendor": {"type": "ORG", "context": "Dogs  ”    destroy all such Personal Data held by Vendor under this Agreement (including any copies and on", "token": "[[REDACTED_719fd489]]"}, "30%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "r rating will be based on the following criteria:\n30% Technical - Ability to meet the minimum technolog", "token": "[[REDACTED_0c77d356]]"}, "User Profile / Group Membership": {"type": "ORG", "context": "cations/web-browsers \nLearning content delivery  \nUser Profile / Group Membership \nContent reporting requirements / transcript rete", "token": "[[REDACTED_0acfea88]]"}, "Testing Environment / Technical Support": {"type": "ORG", "context": "nt reporting requirements / transcript retention \nTesting Environment / Technical Support \nIf there are additional recommendations not outl", "token": "[[REDACTED_a7dffd53]]"}, "35%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": " and cost at the end of the appropriate sections.\n35% Cost - Solution that provides best value\n20% Non-", "token": "[[REDACTED_0782860f]]"}, "20%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "ons.\n35% Cost - Solution that provides best value\n20% Non-Operational Business Requirements\nTechnology ", "token": "[[REDACTED_d0d910f6]]"}, "Non-Operational Business Requirements\nTechnology": {"type": "ORG", "context": "\n35% Cost - Solution that provides best value\n20% Non-Operational Business Requirements\nTechnology security, information protection and security sta", "token": "[[REDACTED_e2e7d9ea]]"}, "General Contract Requirements": {"type": "ORG", "context": "Requirement:  Provide Proposal good through date\n\nGeneral Contract Requirements \n\nThis Vendor contract will be a commercial contr", "token": "[[REDACTED_9c0e90ff]]"}, "15%": {"type": "PERCENT", "context": "a, Past Performance and References will count for 15% of the vendor’s scoring. The following questions ", "token": "[[REDACTED_4664fec3]]"}, "References - List": {"type": "ORG", "context": "\nUnderstanding our business needs and environment\nReferences - List of current clients and the names and contact info", "token": "[[REDACTED_43a4519d]]"}, "the last four years": {"type": "DATE", "context": "hat have been provided comparable services within the last four years.\n\nThe award of the contract to the winning vendor", "token": "[[REDACTED_62e16174]]"}, "Microsoft": {"type": "ORG", "context": "rts must be generated for all training content in Microsoft Excel format. The following information must be r", "token": "[[REDACTED_c2425a5a]]"}, "Adobe PDF": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "osal response should be provided in both Word and Adobe PDF.\n\n", "token": "[[REDACTED_87cc0ac7]]"}, "Vendor Proposal": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "t formatted in both Microsoft Word and Adobe PDF. Vendor Proposal must be complete, and all questions posed in the ", "token": "[[REDACTED_d4e72ded]]"}, "A. Supporting Software Applications/Web-Browsers": {"type": "ORG", "context": "hat are outlined within our current environment.\n\nA. Supporting Software Applications/Web-Browsers   \nThe Help More Dogs delivers various forms of t", "token": "[[REDACTED_98d4a021]]"}, "B. Learning": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "d document files using the following software: \n\n\nB. Learning Content Delivery  \nThe Help More Dogs currently d", "token": "[[REDACTED_592dbb49]]"}, "IP": {"type": "ORG", "context": "many as 15 employees. LMS access is restricted by IP address. \n\nAll learning content has a course/docu", "token": "[[REDACTED_6ceff1fb]]"}, "Phase One": {"type": "ORG", "context": "abled for access. After completing all courses in Phase One, the user will be automatically assigned Phase 2.", "token": "[[REDACTED_aef58929]]"}, "Phase 2": {"type": "ORG", "context": "hase One, the user will be automatically assigned Phase 2. \n \nSearch Engine: All learning material must be ", "token": "[[REDACTED_b2169d7d]]"}, "PDF": {"type": "ORG", "context": " when a course is successfully completed (Word or PDF format). \n\nCustomized Report Retrieval: Reports m", "token": "[[REDACTED_e5a51cf9]]"}, "PowerPoint": {"type": "ORG", "context": "epository: Help More Dogs currently provides PDF, PowerPoint, and Microsoft Word training guides outside of SC", "token": "[[REDACTED_7220ee62]]"}, "SCORM": {"type": "ORG", "context": "eparate platform to design courses and publish in SCORM file format. Vendor would need to provide an inst", "token": "[[REDACTED_5500425e]]"}, "Quiz/Test Assignments": {"type": "ORG", "context": "essible through one single document repository. \n\nQuiz/Test Assignments: Knowledge Assessments are assigned monthly utili", "token": "[[REDACTED_4df11bb4]]"}, "monthly": {"type": "DATE", "context": "t Assignments: Knowledge Assessments are assigned monthly utilizing randomized questions created from all i", "token": "[[REDACTED_86ae74b4]]"}, "Learner": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ng Guides are available for all user type access: Learner, Manager, Administrator. \n\nAdditional Resources \n", "token": "[[REDACTED_ff16915a]]"}, "LOA": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lly assigned courses which have launched while on LOA status upon their return.  Courses stop being ass", "token": "[[REDACTED_cc0fc495]]"}, "Training": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ly lock. An automatic notification is sent to the Training group email inbox when a user has been locked fro", "token": "[[REDACTED_c0012998]]"}, "Groups": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d from the learning profile. \n\nMembership Groups: Groups are identified by group ID, name, and description", "token": "[[REDACTED_293754e1]]"}, "two weeks": {"type": "DATE", "context": "lete” courses, an additional notification is sent two weeks prior to due date and again when it is past due. ", "token": "[[REDACTED_d661b5b6]]"}, "Customized Report Retrieval": {"type": "ORG", "context": "is successfully completed (Word or PDF format). \n\nCustomized Report Retrieval: Reports must be generated for all training conte", "token": "[[REDACTED_77a6bff1]]"}, "Completed": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ployee is in the process of completing the course\nCompleted – employee has completed and passed the course\nEm", "token": "[[REDACTED_6d1ae6b7]]"}, "Employee Information\nName": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ed – employee has completed and passed the course\nEmployee Information\nName (Last, First)\nCountry of residence \nBanking Cente", "token": "[[REDACTED_f7653694]]"}, "Banking Center/Department": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ormation\nName (Last, First)\nCountry of residence \nBanking Center/Department \nUser/profile creation date \n\nImportant: Due to R", "token": "[[REDACTED_65e02bf1]]"}, "E. Testing Environment / Technical Support \nTesting Environment": {"type": "ORG", "context": "es generated must be hidden from the reporting. \n\nE. Testing Environment / Technical Support \nTesting Environment: Platform must provide a testing environment wher", "token": "[[REDACTED_cbe0f8d4]]"}, "LMS Training Guides/Education": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ll-free support line or online ticket entering. \n\nLMS Training Guides/Education: Onboarding technical support to learn how to use", "token": "[[REDACTED_ba0c108d]]"}, "B. Financial Institution": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lease include details on how this is supported. \n\nB. Financial Institution (Banking) Course Catalog \nPlease provide a course", "token": "[[REDACTED_c5728c72]]"}, "the Help More Dogs Learning and Leadership Development Department": {"type": "ORG", "context": "esponses\n\nThe following services are required for the Help More Dogs Learning and Leadership Development Department. Vendors are to provide their best solution for s", "token": "[[REDACTED_38ed24b9]]"}, "Legend of Response Codes": {"type": "ORG", "context": "able. \n\nLegend – Response Codes\nUse the following Legend of Response Codes to indicate the availability of each Feature and/", "token": "[[REDACTED_4dff7524]]"}, "Features and Functional Requirements": {"type": "ORG", "context": "y of each Feature and/or Function\n\n\nThe following Features and Functional Requirements are required unless indicated as “Preferred”.\n\nSU", "token": "[[REDACTED_9facb291]]"}, "Bark Barn-Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d or malicious loss, destruction or alteration of Bark Barn-Help More Dogs files, program information, software and other pr", "token": "[[REDACTED_bcd15e98]]"}, "Non-Disclosure Agreement": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ogs.  If your company is new to Help More Dogs, a Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) was required. If your company is a current ", "token": "[[REDACTED_69a110c9]]"}, "NDA": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ew to Help More Dogs, a Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) was required. If your company is a current vendo", "token": "[[REDACTED_d5e4e8ef]]"}, "Confirm": {"type": "ORG", "context": "viding services to Help More Dogs.\n\nRequirement:  Confirm acceptance of Help More Dogs right to pre-approve", "token": "[[REDACTED_11784916]]"}, "TIME": {"type": "ORG", "context": "u can offer which is either earlier or later than TIME, please clearly include that commitment or limita", "token": "[[REDACTED_f48d04c5]]"}, "Provide Proposal": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "nd review process can be lengthy. \n\nRequirement:  Provide Proposal good through date\n\nGeneral Contract Requirements ", "token": "[[REDACTED_5ca9c5fa]]"}, "CLINET": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ion of a Bark Barn proprietary contract utilizing CLINET standard terms and conditions following Bark Barn", "token": "[[REDACTED_ac4b09c8]]"}, "Acknowledge": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "N AND VALUATION (DATE)\n\n[REDACTED]\n\nRequirement:  Acknowledge and agree to comply if applicable.  \n\nImplementat", "token": "[[REDACTED_59b4f3ad]]"}, "Financial Responsibility  \n\nRequirement:": {"type": "ORG", "context": "dge and agree to comply.\n\nLegal Entity Status and Financial Responsibility  \n\nRequirement: Identify the legal name, type of vendor’s contrac", "token": "[[REDACTED_466c2d3e]]"}, "LLC": {"type": "ORG", "context": " specific company structure e.g. holding company, LLC, wholly owned subsidiary. Describe the overall hi", "token": "[[REDACTED_b008a8f1]]"}, "GmBH": {"type": "GPE", "context": "dor’s contracting entity (as in corporation, LLC, GmBH), the date the entity was established, and locati", "token": "[[REDACTED_66eeb62e]]"}, "State": {"type": "GPE", "context": "d, and location of certifying jurisdiction (as in State, Country). Include description of company ownersh", "token": "[[REDACTED_bdcae83e]]"}, "Sub-Contractors": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ve.\n\nLocation of Vendor and Identification of all Sub-Contractors\n\nHelp More Dogs is responsible for knowing its ve", "token": "[[REDACTED_5f0001a4]]"}, "Help More Dogs": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ne Year Option Years, with the options awarded by Help More Dogs based on performance.\nA Straight 5 year Base Term", "token": "[[REDACTED_f08585c5]]"}, "LOCATION": {"type": "ORG", "context": "lizing facilities or personnel located outside of LOCATION, this must also be disclosed in your proposal. \n\n", "token": "[[REDACTED_abbba32e]]"}, "Representatives and/or Subcontractors": {"type": "ORG", "context": "er in part or in whole, by Vendor, its employees, Representatives and/or Subcontractors on and from a location or locations in one (1) or", "token": "[[REDACTED_35d47d68]]"}, "Order": {"type": "ORG", "context": "d (c) on (i) termination of this Agreement or any Order; or (ii) the written request of Company, Vendor s", "token": "[[REDACTED_f9997eda]]"}, "Vendor’s Representatives": {"type": "ORG", "context": "shall, and shall be responsible for ensuring that Vendor’s Representatives and Subcontractors shall, perform all obligations", "token": "[[REDACTED_00e29fc9]]"}, "annual": {"type": "DATE", "context": "actors successfully complete and implement, on an annual basis, such mandatory training as Company may req", "token": "[[REDACTED_1d5b8872]]"}, "Libel": {"type": "GPE", "context": "erformers, style, characters, plots, or material;\nLibel, trade libel, slander, disparagement of a person,", "token": "[[REDACTED_26c66670]]"}, "Breach": {"type": "ORG", "context": "l, including trade mark dilution and passing-off;\nBreach of contract limited to only those breaches, which", "token": "[[REDACTED_26749120]]"}, "Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ntract means this Agreement.\nPrime Contract means Company’s contract with Department of Commerce\n\n\n[REDACTE", "token": "[[REDACTED_ac30d73f]]"}, "Extortion": {"type": "ORG", "context": "er crime or information theft;\nDenial of service;\nExtortion;\nIntroduction, implantation, or spread of a compu", "token": "[[REDACTED_6c967bf4]]"}, "Introduction": {"type": "ORG", "context": " information theft;\nDenial of service;\nExtortion;\nIntroduction, implantation, or spread of a computer virus;\nLos", "token": "[[REDACTED_a11e7414]]"}, "Loss": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "ion, implantation, or spread of a computer virus;\nLoss of service;\nUnauthorized access or use, including", "token": "[[REDACTED_d256f163]]"}, "Department of Commerce Exclusion": {"type": "ORG", "context": "han as stated in proposal.\n\nVendor Declaration on Department of Commerce Exclusion\n\nVendor must represent and warrant that neither i", "token": "[[REDACTED_51a83117]]"}, "Proposal": {"type": "GPE", "context": " agree to comply. Disclose status as requested in Proposal. \n\nSpecial Termination by Department of Commerce\n", "token": "[[REDACTED_2c9f2c6e]]"}, "Current Department of Commerce Contractor": {"type": "ORG", "context": "mply. Disclose status as requested in Proposal. \n\nCurrent Department of Commerce Contractor\n\nVendor must identify if it is currently under co", "token": "[[REDACTED_c1d104f3]]"}, "Schedule": {"type": "PERSON", "context": ", REGULATION contains the clauses attached in the Schedule, entitled “FAR Clauses”, and in turn Bark Barn is", "token": "[[REDACTED_f1554893]]"}, "the Department of Commerce’s  Help More Dogs": {"type": "ORG", "context": "-Help More Dogs has certain obligations to manage the Department of Commerce’s  Help More Dogs under the  Help More Dogs Prime Contract (the “Pr", "token": "[[REDACTED_0c50df55]]"}, "60 days": {"type": "DATE", "context": " with Bark Barn, such termination to be effective 60 days following delivery of such notice. Bark Barn sole", "token": "[[REDACTED_6d078021]]"}, "the final day": {"type": "DATE", "context": "liverables provided and services rendered through the final day on which the Vendor provided deliverables and per", "token": "[[REDACTED_77bdad9a]]"}, "Travel": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ply\n\nTravel Related Expenses\n\nVendor expenses for Travel, Lodging and Per Diem must be pre-approved by Hel", "token": "[[REDACTED_64f1117a]]"}, "Lodging and Per Diem": {"type": "ORG", "context": "vel Related Expenses\n\nVendor expenses for Travel, Lodging and Per Diem must be pre-approved by Help More Dogs and will b", "token": "[[REDACTED_ce2890f7]]"}, "the Department of Commerce REGULATION": {"type": "ORG", "context": "e reimbursed by Help More Dogs in accordance with the Department of Commerce REGULATION.  \n\nRequirement:  Acknowledge and agree to comply", "token": "[[REDACTED_c64bc2a3]]"}, "WEBSITE": {"type": "ORG", "context": "any Renewal Terms. The REGULATION may be found at WEBSITE. Vendor further understands it is responsible for", "token": "[[REDACTED_1f71068d]]"}, "Vendors": {"type": "ORG", "context": "protected. Under various sections of the contract Vendors will be required to: provide documented security ", "token": "[[REDACTED_3b253900]]"}, "Trojan": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "uitry or any automatic restraint, trapdoor, worm, Trojan horse or other harmful code that would cause soft", "token": "[[REDACTED_40759b25]]"}, "Personal Data Protection": {"type": "ORG", "context": "\n\nRequirement:  Acknowledge and agree to comply.\n\nPersonal Data Protection – REDACTED\n\n1.1 The provisions of this Section en", "token": "[[REDACTED_272fbff0]]"}, "Processing": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ational measures for ensuring the security of the Processing.  If required under the Data Protection Laws, suc", "token": "[[REDACTED_a009595b]]"}, "Personal Data": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ta Protection Laws.\nVendor shall not transfer any Personal Data outside of the   REDACTED Economic Area or any ot", "token": "[[REDACTED_28937310]]"}, "REDACTED": {"type": "ORG", "context": "receiving the Services is established outside the REDACTED but is offering goods or services to, is monitori", "token": "[[REDACTED_98d51963]]"}, "Data Protection Laws": {"type": "ORG", "context": "     including notifying Company of any breach of Data Protection Laws in accordance with the “Help More Dogs  ”   . \nVe", "token": "[[REDACTED_7e37a076]]"}, "Vendor and Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": "the Services and to the rights and obligations of Vendor and Company under this Agreement:\n“Company” shall include Aff", "token": "[[REDACTED_5744a14b]]"}, "Affiliates of Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": "any under this Agreement:\n“Company” shall include Affiliates of Company and where applicable, “Vendor” shall mean and inc", "token": "[[REDACTED_a4aff8c3]]"}, "Affiliates": {"type": "ORG", "context": " and use of all Personal Data that Vendor and its Affiliates and Subcontractors Process in connection with the", "token": "[[REDACTED_65dfdc58]]"}, "the General Data Protection Regulation": {"type": "ORG", "context": "A PROTECTION –   REDACTED ECONOMIC AREA,” include the General Data Protection Regulation (EU 2016/679).\n1.3 To the extent Vendor’s Service", "token": "[[REDACTED_036f0df7]]"}, "EU": {"type": "ORG", "context": "” include the General Data Protection Regulation (EU 2016/679).\n1.3 To the extent Vendor’s Services in", "token": "[[REDACTED_e430d8c6]]"}, "Vendor’s Services": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ction Regulation (EU 2016/679).\n1.3 To the extent Vendor’s Services include or require the Processing of Personal Dat", "token": "[[REDACTED_8c31623e]]"}, "the Processing of Personal Data": {"type": "ORG", "context": "milar requests; or (ii) any complaint relating to the Processing of Personal Data, including allegations that the Processing infrin", "token": "[[REDACTED_15c5051a]]"}, "Processed": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ivered or made available to Vendor by Company, or Processed by Vendor on behalf of Company, under or pursuant", "token": "[[REDACTED_d3a72079]]"}, "the Parties that Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": " Vendor agrees as follows:\nIt is the intention of the Parties that Company will be the data controller and Vendor will be a ", "token": "[[REDACTED_d0b0d76d]]"}, "the Personal Data Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": "or will be a data processor.  Vendor will Process the Personal Data Company provides to Vendor only (i) as needed to provide ", "token": "[[REDACTED_55640606]]"}, "Vendor’s Processing of Personal Data": {"type": "ORG", "context": "on and the nature, scope, context and purposes of Vendor’s Processing of Personal Data, as well as the risk of varying likelihood and se", "token": "[[REDACTED_7aed5261]]"}, "the Personal Data Processing": {"type": "ORG", "context": "pplicable Laws.\nTaking into account the nature of the Personal Data Processing and the information available to Vendor.  Vendor ", "token": "[[REDACTED_ec4f8ca0]]"}, "Process Personal Data": {"type": "ORG", "context": " . \nVendor will ensure that persons authorized to Process Personal Data have committed themselves to confidentiality or a", "token": "[[REDACTED_bd8ee943]]"}, "Processing of Personal Data": {"type": "ORG", "context": "t disclose or transfer Personal Data to, or allow Processing of Personal Data by, any third party (including Vendor’s Affiliate", "token": "[[REDACTED_71894849]]"}, "Vendor’s Services for Company": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ion Laws.\nj.\tTo the extent they are applicable to Vendor’s Services for Company, Vendor will (a) maintain all records with specif", "token": "[[REDACTED_57cf40b6]]"}, "the Data Protection Laws": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ntain all records with specificity as required by the Data Protection Laws, including of the nature and use of all Personal ", "token": "[[REDACTED_95f4bda1]]"}, "the Department of Commerce FAR Supplement": {"type": "ORG", "context": "ontractor.  In accordance with the REGULATION and the Department of Commerce FAR Supplement (DFARS), and in accordance with REGULATION“Clause", "token": "[[REDACTED_940c7a6e]]"}, "Officer/Department of Commerce": {"type": "ORG", "context": "\n\nCLAUSES INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE\n \nContracting Officer/Department of Commerce shall mean the Company. \nContractor means the Sel", "token": "[[REDACTED_049971e7]]"}, "Seller": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "rce shall mean the Company. \nContractor means the Seller/Vendor.\n       Contract means this Agreement.\nPri", "token": "[[REDACTED_b3b8e8cc]]"}, "FAR Flowdown Clauses for Subcontracts for Non-Commercial Products or Services": {"type": "ORG", "context": "t with Department of Commerce\n\n\n[REDACTED]\n\nII.   FAR Flowdown Clauses for Subcontracts for Non-Commercial Products or Services\nIn addition to the clauses set forth above, incor", "token": "[[REDACTED_694f37f2]]"}, "REDACTED Flowdown Clauses for Subcontracts": {"type": "ORG", "context": " are defined at REDACTED).  \n\n[REDACTED] \n\nIII.   REDACTED Flowdown Clauses for Subcontracts in Support of Prime Contract No. REDACTED\nIn addi", "token": "[[REDACTED_6b7ddd13]]"}, "Implementation and Timeline\n\nProvide": {"type": "ORG", "context": "Acknowledge and agree to comply if applicable.  \n\nImplementation and Timeline\n\nProvide a brief overview of your implementation methodolo", "token": "[[REDACTED_e819f115]]"}, "Vendor Selection Criteria": {"type": "ORG", "context": "\n\n\n\nPast Performance and References\n\nAs stated in Vendor Selection Criteria, Past Performance and References will count for 1", "token": "[[REDACTED_f8dc2e82]]"}, "Accounting, Human Resource": {"type": "ORG", "context": "llowing qualifications:\n\nOrganization support for Accounting, Human Resource (HR) and/or Payroll in Italy for entities headqua", "token": "[[REDACTED_d81b5280]]"}, "Payroll": {"type": "ORG", "context": "upport for Accounting, Human Resource (HR) and/or Payroll in Italy for entities headquartered outside of It", "token": "[[REDACTED_7d8958a8]]"}, "Italy": {"type": "GPE", "context": "ll in Italy for entities headquartered outside of Italy.\n\nPreferably a Financial Services organization.\n\n", "token": "[[REDACTED_d4af75eb]]"}, "3) year": {"type": "DATE", "context": "for one or both contract term scenarios. \n\nThree (3) year Base Term plus two (2) One Year Option Years, wit", "token": "[[REDACTED_bcc02667]]"}, "Base Term": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "More Dogs based on performance.\nA Straight 5 year Base Term.\n\nVendors must include any volume or term discoun", "token": "[[REDACTED_2e3ec193]]"}, "5 year": {"type": "DATE", "context": "y Help More Dogs based on performance.\nA Straight 5 year Base Term.\n\nVendors must include any volume or te", "token": "[[REDACTED_227af0b4]]"}, "the General Contract Business Requirements": {"type": "ORG", "context": " the contract. Note: The reference for this is in the General Contract Business Requirements, Contract Term and Pricing. \n\nProposal response s", "token": "[[REDACTED_0042a235]]"}, "Word": {"type": "PERSON", "context": "g. \n\nProposal response should be provided in both Word and Adobe PDF.\n\n", "token": "[[REDACTED_b064c2b2]]"}}